Dimas Abdul Aziz

Pangandaran, West Java, Indonesia



diimasaziiz@gmail.com





linkedin.com/in/diimasaziiz

Phttp://sandekala.github.io/Portfolio

Summary

Experienced in Back Office for more than 4 years, also has experience as Assistant Supervisor / Coordinator for almost 2 years. Likes work in the IT field and also has a passion in Web Development at the Front End Developer by having more than 2 important certificates for website development such as JavaScript, jQuery, Responsive Web Design, etc.

Experience

Mbg Assistant Supervisor

PT. Bringin Gigantara

Nov 2020 - Mar 2022 (1 year 5 months)

- Managed 8 employees in 2 division.
- Responsible that all Cash Handling operational activities are in Standard Operational Procedure in both division.
- Controlling and monitoring the movement and development of the team in the field to ensuring all issues has been handled and in order to achieve the 100% performance.
- Communicating and coordinating both internally and externally with among 2 departments.
- Responsible for additional cash with a minimum amount of 200 million rupiah.

Monitoring Monitoring

PT. Bringin Gigantara

Nov 2017 - Oct 2020 (3 years)

- Receive and follow up on every order and problems from customers to related parts and make sure problems solved to achieve 100% performance.
- Coordinate with the Monitoring Desk of the E-Channel, regarding the position of ATM balances that are in a low cash condition and making replenishment orders in every 2 hours.
- Make sure for preparing the necessary documents for each CIT, ATM Replenishment and FLM activities.
- Making Daily Activity Report.

Custody Officer

PT. Bringin Gigantara

Mar 2015 - Oct 2017 (2 years 8 months)

- First Level Maintenance ATM.
- Replenishment and Preventive Maintenance ATM.

Education

Universitas Bina Sarana Informatika

Diploma of Education, Information Technology 2017 - 2020

Licenses & Certifications

Certified Software Development Associate (CSDA) - Badan Nasional Sertifikasi Profesi

Issued Feb 2021 - Expires Feb 2024

- (A) Responsive Web Design freeCodeCamp
- S Introduction to Programming Using JavaScript Sololearn
- S jQuery Course Sololearn
- JavaScript Udemy: Online Courses

Skills

Web Design • JavaScript • Supervisory Skills • Team Management • Microsoft Excel • Problem Solving • Leadership • Customer Service Management • Analytical Skills • Management